hey guys coach bre andas here this is
the Beast St Squat and I've Never filmed
a video of this but uh I really like
it um I think that if your goal is to
find a single leg exercise that
transfers to the full squat um the best
then I would go with this
exercise and it's going to mimic the
same range of motion as a squat but
you're going to put most of the emphasis
on one leg so I'm going to unrack
the bar belt I like to do high bar and
all I'm going to do is get this leg just
I like to point it out and I like this
leg to be straight ahead really when I
squat my stance would be like this but
this leg is going to be straight ahead
because I'm going to try to keep most of
my weight on this leg and this leg I'm
just going to kind of keep it here for
stability but most of my again most of
my weight is on this leg and I try to
keep it there the whole time throughout
the whole range of motion so it looks
like
this and then you would switch this
leg so again
I'm not sure how much you keep U like
how much weight you really keep on one
leg and the other but just try to think
this the non-working leg is just there
for stability sink down into a full
range of motion try to keep most of the
weight on the leg you're trying to work
and uh if you can't do the if you can't
go all the way down like if that hurts
your hip then just go to parallel
another thing is some people like to
stand on a plate when they do these
and they'll kind of go like this and
they think that helps so like this they
think this helps provide less assistance
I've tried both and I like it just on
flat ground but just be aware of that
all right thanks for watching